omnitechsupport.com 2015-05-30

# Tech Support | IT Support | Online IT Support - Omnitechsupport.com

Annual Unlimited   
PC Maintenance & Technical  
Support for Just $299.99 a year

Call 1-800-966-9940

Support for Microsoft® Office

| 

OmniTechSupport collects personal information when you register or fill out any forms on our site. As OmniTechSupport wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose its information practices. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact OmniTechSupport Privacy Information Department by emailing [ support@omnitechsupport.com](mailto:support@omnitechsupport.com)

OmniTechSupport is vigilant about protecting your data and personal privacy. This statement describes the following: 

  * What information we collect from visitors to our website 
  * How we use the information collected 
  * How and with whom the information is shared 
  * How you can opt-in to or opt-out of information collection and use of the information 
  * Our policy on correcting and updating personal identifier information. 

**What information we collect**

OmniTechSupport collects information such as your name, email address, zip code and other personal information to verify your identity. OmniTechSupport does not collect such information as your social security number, email passwords, or driver's license number. 

OmniTechSupport also automatically receives and records information provided by you on our server logs including information obtained from your browser, including your IP address and the page(s) you request. 

We also receive from you certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.OmniTechSupport. More information about OmniTechSupport use of "cookies" is discussed below. 

In order to tailor our communications to you in the future as well as improve our products and services we may also ask you to provide us with consumer satisfaction information and other data regarding your personal or professional interests, experience with our services, and more detailed contact preferences. You always have the option of choosing not to provide us with this type of information. We do not use "cookies" to collect any information when you access [ www.omnitechsupport.com](http://www.omnitechsupport.com/)

**Use of Data**

OmniTechSupport uses your information to complete your transaction, to better understand your needs and provide you with excellent service and assistance. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, including fulfillment of services and promotional offers, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, to personalize our Web sites for you, to manage and renew your subscription(s) and to resolve your issues with our services. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and fraud protection, and are not used for any other purposes without your permission.

**Use of Your Email Address**

OmniTechSupport does not sell, rent or share your email address with third parties. If you provide us with your email address when you register as a customer or for a service, we may occasionally send you email with recommendations or notices of new services and prices. Unless you opt out, we may use your registration name and email address to send you promotional materials from OmniTechSupport that we think may interest you.

Separately, we send service notifications via email to keep you informed about the status of your service orders and to provide updates and technical notices. These messages are essential to the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our services. Therefore there is no opt-out available for service notifications and these messages cannot be blocked.

We follow strict best practices for email marketing and customer contact. For more information on our practices, please see "Use of Data." For advertising purposes, visitor and customer information is statistically aggregated and reported to advertisers. However, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you, such as your name, email address or transaction history. 

**Links**

OmniTechSupport contains links to other Web sites that are not owned or operated by OmniTechSupport. As such, OmniTechSupport does not accept liability for misuse of any information by any Web site to which we may link. Please read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

**Log Files**

OmniTechSupport maintains log files of visitors to our site. Any information gathered in these log files is not linked personally identifying information. Log files manage traffic load in order to provide reliable service to visitors and customers. Information that is collected and maintained in the log files includes IP addresses and browser types. 

**Feedback**

We collect user feedback, and from this feedback we derive user testimonials that appear on the website. These testimonials are used only after we have informed and obtained permission from the sender of the testimonial. 

**Access/Correct/Update/Delete User Information**

You can access, update, correct, or delete the personal information held by OmniTechSupport by contacting OmniTechSupport Privacy Information Department at [ support@omnitechsupport.com](mailto:support@omnitechsupport.com)

**Information Security**

All information gathered on the site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only. The OmniTechSupport web site is regularly tested for security breaches to ensure that all information collected is secure from unauthorized viewing. Personal information on our customers is protected in transit via HTTPS and SSL security. 

**Retention of Information**

OmniTechSupport will keep personal information of its users for as long as they are registered subscribers or users of our products, and for a reasonable time thereafter. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we make a material (non-editorial) change to our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our site so our users are aware of the change. If we make a significant change to the way we use, treat or disclose personal information, we will notify users by email. 

* * *

**DISCLAIMER:** omnitechsupport.com is an independent service provider of remote tech support. Third party trademarks, brand names, products and services is only referential and Omni Tech Support hereby disclaims any sponsorship, affiliation or endorsement of or by any such third party. 

* * *
